Entrepreneur Internet www.accentium.com Co-founder Grew startup to 60+ employees across India Topline INR 5Cr Highly Profitable! Jul 2007 - Sep 2010

ankur warikoo

warikoo@gmail.com in.linkedin.com/in/warikoo



5+ years of experience as an entrepreneur and management consultant very lucky to done a lot in life already! and the real fun hasnt even started!

Awarded the ISB Young Leader Award for leadership excellence. Only 4 students in the batch of 345 received it

That medal is going to the grave with the body!!

Ms, Physics/Statistics Michigan State Univ Full scholarship! Much to dad's comfort! Bought the 1st computer with the stipend! such joy... April 2004

Consultant **NIS Sparta**

Registered average target achievement of 117% in the 4 review quarters Left it for ISB

Apr 2004 - Mar 2005

Management Consultant A.T. Kearney

Made crazy excel sheets, wore nice suits, got paid a lot and met some of the smartest people ever! Learnt how to structure

May 2006 - Apr 2009

Photography - stress buster! Won 4 national competitions in 6 years of association with photography. Work published in National Geographic

(Online) and 2 Coffee Table Books Public Speaking - bournvita! Won 21 debates as a student at the University of Delhi. Regular speaker at MBA schools on

areas such as Internet, Entrepreneurship. Spoke at MDI, FMS, ISB in the last 6 months

PASSIONATE ABOUT ENTREPRENEURSHIP Regularly mentor entrepreneurs on multiple aspects of their business PASSIONATE ABOUT PROBLEM SOLVING Think its got to do with the zodiac! Excel FREAK! And all decisions have to pass PASSIONATE ABOUT PEOPLE through it! Ability to listen more than speak Crave for people with the right attitude! Believe in employee first policy

Fastest promotion in **ATK India History**;

Promoted to Associate in 1.5 years against firm average of 2.5 years

Humbled!

BS, Physics Hindu College, **Delhi University**

Paid for the tuition through debating wins! Actually, made much more ISB CGPA: 3.43 (Top 11% of Class) MSU CGPA: 3.91 (Ranked First in Class) Hindu CGPA: 3.04 (Ranked First in Class)

Yup!! Nerdddd!



- > Professional with 5+ years of experience as an Internet Entrepreneur and Management Consultant
- > Hands-on experience of building a business along with a comprehensive understanding of the Indian Internet Industry
- > Strong analytical skills with a penchant towards problem solving matched with effective inter-personal skills
- > Passionate about entrepreneurship, the Internet and creating large-scaled impact

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



Co-Founder, Accentium Web

Jul 2007 - Sep 2010

Part of the 3-member founding team at Accentium Web. Part-Time capacity till April 2009

Accentium Web is one of India's fastest growing Internet companies, with a portfolio of 6 products such as SecondShaadi (#1 Remarriage), StudyNation (#1 Education), Gaadi (#2 Auto) and SitaGita (#2 Women's)

- Accentium reached topline of INR 5Cr (2009) with a 50% y-o-y growth; profitable since its 18th month
- Grown to 60+ employees across Delhi, Mumbai, Hyderabad, Pune and Bangalore
- Product managed StudyNation and championed its rise to #1 Education Portal in only 9 months. Handled all aspects across product design & development, sales & operations
- De-facto HR Head, managing recruitment and retention; Attrition of less than 1%
- Expert understanding of the Internet Industry, online advertising market and product development & design

ATKEARNEY Associate

May 2006 - Apr 2009

Engaged with top clients across Media & Entertainment, Real Estate, Oil & Gas and Private Equity

- Fastest promotion in ATK India History; Promoted to Associate in 1.5 years against firm average of 2.5 years
- Led multiple engagements from PE investment evaluation to market entry strategy to cost-reduction initiatives
- Cross-cultural exposure through engagements in Middle East and USA in addition to India-based ones

NIS Sparta Consultant

Apr 2004 - Apr 2005

NIS Sparta Ltd. is Asia's largest corporate training consultancy with turnover of Rs. 500 million

- Registered average target achievement of 117% in the 4 review quarters. Client satisfaction stood at highest 4.89/5.00
- Fetched India's largest order for psychometric tools by statistically designing & developing recruitment tool

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS



Post-Graduate Program In Management (MBA, Finance)

Apr 2006

CGPA: 3.43/4.00 (Top 11% amongst Class of 360)

- · Awarded the ISB Young Leader Award for academic and extra-curricular excellence. Only 1% of batch received the award
- Developed statistical macroeconomic model to predict yearly growth of employment (organized sector) in the Indian economy, for India's leading HR consulting firm. 1st time such an employment index was introduced in India

MICHIGAN STATE

MS, Physics

Apr 2004

CGPA of 3.91/4.00; Rank 1/103

- Derived a 'never-before published' age for the Milky Way using sophisticated statistical tools, as a research assistant



BS, Physics

Aggregate of 76.29% over 3 years; Rank 1/23 (College); Top 5% in Delhi University

- Recipient of the National Scholarship awarded by the Department of Physics to the top students of the department

PERSONAL AND BEYOND WORK

Entrepreneurship - Passionate about entrepreneurship; Regularly mentor entrepreneurs on multiple aspects of their business

- Alum Member of the ISB Entrepreneurship Cell, aimed at encouraging current students to take the plunge

Photography - Won 4 national competitions in 6 years of association with photography

- Work published in National Geographic (Online) and 2 Coffee Table Books

Public Speaking - Regular speaker at MBA schools on areas such as Internet, Entrepreneurship. Spoke at MDI, FMS, ISB in the last 6 months

- Won 21 debates as a student at the University of Delhi